{
    "id": "be9bd286925a45259bd857c435f086fb",
    "title": "Would Or Should",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "170d7b9cfdf942feabf7a7d7613a442d",
            "title": "Would Or Should",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The postman …………………. be here soon.",
                    "description": "We use should to indicate possibility.",
                    "answers": [
                        "should",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………. we invite Mark?",
                    "description": "We use should to ask for a suggestion.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Should",
                        "Would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ………………………… be told.",
                    "description": "We use should to express necessity.",
                    "answers": [
                        "should",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "People …………………….. drive more carefully.",
                    "description": "We use should to express necessity.",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You …………………………… do things like that.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "wouldn't",
                        "shouldn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………………. come tomorrow if I got time.",
                    "description": "In the second conditional, we use a past tense in the if-clause and would + infinitive in the main clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………………. be grateful for an early reply.",
                    "description": "Both would and should can be used with the first person pronouns with little difference of meaning.",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………………. you like some help?",
                    "description": "We use would in polite offers and requests.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Would",
                        "Should",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………………. I go and see the police?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Should",
                        "Would",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I knew that I ………………………… talk to her, but it seemed too difficult.",
                    "description": "Should indicates necessity or obligation. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………………. have sent the money this morning, but I forgot.",
                    "description": "Should have is often used to talk about past events that did not happen. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "should",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ……………………………. have shouted at her – it really upset her.",
                    "description": "Should not have is often used to talk about unwanted things that happened. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "should not",
                        "would not",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}